<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MananVPatel</string>
    <string name="about_me">I am an ambitious and motivated software developer with a bachelor\'s
        degree in Computer Science and a minor in Management Information Systems from Pennsylvania State
        University. Additionally, I was a resident assistant and a grader/TA, as well as an active member of
        multiple clubs and organizations on campus. I have built multiple Android applications and this portfolio
        app \"from the ground up.\" I am actively seeking full time employment in the Software
        Engineering/Development field. </string>
    <string name="home_desc" formatted="false">I love building, designing, reading, &amp; cracking logic puzzles.</string>
    <string-array name="projects_array">
        <item>ATM.go</item>
        <item>Classic Sanskrit App</item>
        <item>Court Counter App</item>
        <item>SPYTeam (Senior Project)</item>
        <item>Pebble Watch App</item>
        <item>Portfolio Website</item>
        <item>Trivia App</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="atmDesc">• Worked with a team of 5 hackers to build a facial recognition web interface and an android app for Capital
        One in order to accelerate the deposit/withdrawal process. \n\n• Analyzed a multitude of the real public-facing data provided
        by the Nessie API in order to create an ”on the go” banking experience for Capital One customers.</string>
    <string name="sansDesc">• Built a multi-screen app using intents, external libraries, interfaces, and custom classes that enables users to
        learn Sanskrit words, numbers, phrases, and colors.\n\n
        • Each of the categories are implemented using ListView and Custom ArrayAdapters that recycles views to enhance response time.</string>
    <string name="courtCounterDesc">• Built an app using intents, interfaces, and custom classes that enables users to
        email custom order information to the person buying the goods.</string>
    <string name="spDesc">• Implemented a web application which pulls project/organization data from Git-Hub and analyzes it using machine learning.\n\n
        • The analyzed data isused to evaluate team members placed on a project, based on their performance statistics pulled from GitHub.</string>
    <string name="pwDesc">• Created a smart watch app using Pebble libraries, AccuWeather API and IBM Watson’s Natural Language Processing API.\n\n
        • It displays optimal times throughout the day for outdoor activity based on a verbal query made by the user.</string>
    <string name="portfolioDesc">• Built this portfolio website from the group up using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. It is hosted on Google\'s App
        Engine using Python for backend and the domain is secured through Google Domains. </string>
    <string name="triviaDesc">• Built an app using multiple intents, custom classes, listview, checkboxs, radio buttons and a spinner.\n\n
        • The app enables the user to pass data by saving states in between activites.</string>
    <string name="RADesc">• Made a positive impact on the community by constructing educational, social, recreational, and
        cultural programs.\n\n• Served as a visible campus leader, employee and representative for the Office of Residence Life and Penn State Erie,
        The Behrend College.</string>
    <string name="TADesc">• Assisted students with questions and concerns regarding labs and homework
        assignments.\n\n• Collaborated with the professor for future assignments.</string>

    <string-array name="workExp_array">
        <item>Resident Assistant</item>
        <item>Teaching Assistant</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="title_activity_resume_viewer">ResumeViewer</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="title_activity_resumeviewer">resumeviewer</string>
</resources>
